{
    "subject": "resource/Posidonius",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Panaetius",
    "human_readable": "Posidonius was influenced by Panaetius.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9292358756065369,
            "question": "Panaetius was a significant influence on whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8894128799438477,
            "question": "Who influenced Posidonius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7994074821472168,
            "question": "Name a figure who had an impact on Posidonius."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.789788544178009,
            "question": "What intellectual connection existed between Panaetius and Posidonius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7722471952438354,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Posidonius and Panaetius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7429207563400269,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Posidonius and Panaetius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7150636315345764,
            "question": "Panaetius's teachings impacted which individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.696929395198822,
            "question": "Who learned from Panaetius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5298821926116943,
            "question": "Can you identify the source of inspiration for Posidonius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17241297662258148,
            "question": "Who can be considered a teacher or mentor to Posidonius?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Posidonius was influenced by Panaetius.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5975_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify the source of inspiration for Posidonius?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5975_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who learned from Panaetius?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5975_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Panaetius's teachings impacted which individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5975_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5975_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple as follows:\n\n* The first document mentions that Posidonius was a student of Panaetius, which suggests that Posidonius was influenced by him.\n* Later documents further emphasize the close relationship between Panaetius and Posidonius, with Posidonius being referred to as one of the main representatives of Middle Stoicism alongside Panaetius. This implies a significant influence from Panaetius on Posidonius's thought.\n\nOverall, the information in the documents provides strong evidence that supports the triple \"Posidonius was influenced by Panaetius\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Posidonius of Apamea (Syria) was a Stoic philosopher and student of Panaetius,\" indicating that Posidonius was indeed influenced by Panaetius."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}